竜ヶ峰… 帝人です
I'm Ryugamine...Mikado.
No way! That's really you, Kida?
紀田君！ 紀田君なの？
Gang activity has been declining recently, too.
最近はカラーギャングも減ったよ
They got into a fight with some Saitama
guys and a bunch of people got arrested.
埼玉と抗争やって何十人もパクられてさ
I'm Sonohara Anri. I hope the year goes well.
園原杏里です
よろしくお願いします
Harima!
張間さん！
I thought you were someone else!
人違いでした！
You pledged to become a fine Ikebukuroer,
so show us all and overcome this tribulation!
立派な池袋人になると誓ったのなら
この試練を乗り越えてみせるのだ！
I found you, my...love.
見つけた… オレの愛
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
返します！ 返します！
Please, forgive me.
ど… どうか お許しを
This is bad.
This is really bad.
It's all my fault, Celty.
僕のせいだ セルティ
僕がつまらない仕事を引き受けたせいで…
It's all because I made you take that ridiculous job.
I should've finished it without any problems;
it's because that thing showed up randomly.
仕事はすぐに片づくはずだったんだ
そこに たまたまあれが現れただけで…
You're not human. You're a monster! A monster! A monster!
人間じゃない 化け物 化け物 化け物…
You heard a voice coming from your wound?
「傷口から声が聞こえた」？
It called me a monster!
私のことを化け物と言った
What a rude jerk. It should've at least called you an enchantress.
なんて失礼なヤツだ
せめて魔性の女と言ってほしいね
What is that thing?
あれはなんだ？
What if it's an alien?!
Celty...
セルティ…
Is that supposed to be funny?
それは笑うところかい？
Mo-Monster!
ば… 化け物～！
Let's go!
行くぞ！
This city is apparently comprised of jokes, caprices, and coincidences.
この街は冗談と気まぐれと偶然で出来ているらしい
Saika has entered the chat room.
Humans
The strong
Hope
Love
Humans who love and hope
Because hope is strong people human love. Because because because hope is is.
I
am I, so I hope.
...
Strong, people
Hope
I, love
because
This situation may also be one of God's jokes or caprices.
このシチュエーションも 神様の気まぐれか冗談か…
There are thirty-seven girls I've fallen in love with at first sight since entering high school.
入学式でひと目ぼれした３７人の女子
And like a plot twist in a drama, I get to walk home from school
with one of my top five, who happens to be this girl with glasses...
そのトップ５に入る最上級メガネっ子と
ドラマみたいな展開で一緒に下校することになったってぇのに
But this country bumpkin is getting in the way.
とんだ野暮天に邪魔されるとは いや 参ったね
That must have been pretty tough on you.
この前は大変だったね
Um, yeah...
うん
This isn't good.
ダメだ こりゃ…
I was totally surprised back there.
あんときは驚いたぜ まったく～
I can't believe you ran away without me.
帝人に抜け駆けされるなんてな
It's wasn't like that...
抜け駆けって そんな…
No way! Mikado!
うそ！ 帝人～！
But you did help me.
でも 助かったぜ
If I were you, I wouldn't have passed up a chance like that.
オレがお前の立場なら あんなチャンスは逃しやしない
Right now we'd be in West Gate Park voicing our love to each other...
今ごろ二人は西口公園で愛を語り合う間柄
And on that note, please go out with me!
ってことで つきあって！
Wai—, Kida!
ちょっ… 紀田君！
Umm, I...
あの… 私…
You don't have to answer right away.
すぐ返事しなくていいから
There are currently seven girls I'm waiting to hear from,
and I'm still deciding which one I'll actually date.
今返事待ちの子が７人いて
どの子とつきあうか調整中だから
You don't have to take him seriously, Sonohara.
園原さん まともに相手しなくていいよ
He'll just tire you out.
疲れるだけだから
He makes it sound like he's toying with you, but
it's no big deal. Even if he hits on you, ultimately—
それに遊んでるようなこと言ってて 大したことないし
ナンパしても 結局…
Hey, you, Mikado!
おい こら 帝人！
This guy's my best friend, Ryugamine Mikado.
こいつ 竜ヶ峰帝人はオレの親友
He's a country bumpkin who's only been in Ikebukuro for a few days.
池袋に出てきてまだ数日のお上りさん
Even though he's unsophisticated and naïve, he's
oddly stubborn and someone you just can't leave alone.
純朴で世間知らずなくせに 妙に頑固なところもあって
なぜかほうっておけない存在
I'm somehow involved in a love triangle with this pure boy.
そんなピュアボーイとオレが思わぬ三角関係
Is this what they call "youth?"
これが青春ってやつですか？
Ow, that hurt—
痛ぁ～！
C'mon, Kida!
You're...quite friendly with each other.
仲いいんですね
Yes, we are.
はい いいんです
We don't want to be, but we're inseparable.
腐れ縁ですけど
Uncle, uncle, uncle!
ギブ ギブ ギブ！
To explain how this all came to be...
なんでこうなったかっつうと
We'll have to retrace our steps back to the opening ceremony.
話は始業式までさかのぼる
I'm Yagiri Seiji.
矢霧誠二です
I hope the year goes well.
よろしくお願いします
Well then, Yagiri, you can sit down now.
さあ 矢霧
早く席に着きなさい
I won't need to.
着きません
Huh?
I don't think I'll be coming to school for a while—no, I might not ever come again.
僕 学校にしばらく来れないと思います
いや もう来ないかもしれません
It's something very important to me.
僕にとっては一生のとても大事なことなんです
I have no time to waste with the likes of you.
あなたたちにつきあってる暇はないんです
Please, excuse me.
失礼します
Yagiri, wait. I said, "Wait!"
おい 矢霧
待て… 待ちなさい
The world is full of different types of people...
の中にはいろんなヤツがいるもんだなぁと
Yagiri, wait!
Or so Mikado tells me.
あとで帝人から聞いて思ったわけだが…
Please, wait!
待ってください！
Could this be what it's like to fall in love?
Yagiri, isn't there something—
それがまさにフォーリンラブの瞬間！
I don't know!
My chest throbs just by having her smile at me!
キュートな笑顔にドキ胸～！
Bu-But...being absent on your first day of school...
Well, I guess she wasn't smiling, but still...
ははっ… いや 笑顔じゃなかったが
I said I don't know!
知らないったら！
Wait!
待って！
Umm...
あの～…
Is something wrong?
どうかしました？
Anyway, that's the day I immediately updated the
number one ranked girl on my list of possible girlfriends.
とにかく オレの彼女候補リストの最上位ランクに速攻記録されたその子と
今日…
Hey, Sonohara.
おい 園原
You on your way home?
今 帰りか？
Yes.
はい
Hey, Sonohara, something's bugging you, right?
なあ 園原
何か困ってることがあるんじゃないか？
Maybe you're being bullied or you're involved in some trouble?
いじめとか 厄介事に巻き込まれているとか
No...
いえ…
If something ever happens, tell me right away.
何かあったらすぐオレに言うんだぞ
I'm okay...
大丈夫です
Is that so?
そうか？
Oh yeah, Harima still hasn't come to school yet, has she?
そういえば張間はまだ学校に来ないか
Even though you two are in the same class...
せっかく一緒のクラスになれたのになぁ
I worked hard to get you two in the same class, you know.
あれだって苦労したんだぞ お前と同じクラスにするの
Mr. Saitou from your middle school also insisted that you two be together.
中学の斉藤先生からくれぐれもよろしくと頼まれて
So you don't have to hesitate.
だからお前も遠慮することはないんだぞ？
That's right, how about I take you home today?
そうだ 今日はオレが送っていってやろう
You do know that The Slasher appeared in Ikebukuro again, don't you?
知ってるだろ？ 池袋でまた切り裂き魔が出たって
Mr. Nasujima, are you sexually harassing her?!
那須島先生 セクハラっすかぁ？
Jeez, making our glasses-wearing class rep scream?
わっ！ いたいけなメガネ委員長に声まで出させて
Isn't that full-on sexual harassment?
本格的なセクシュアルハラスメントってやつっすかぁ？
Or is it more like sexy embarrassment?
むしろセクシーハラショーっすかぁ？
C'mon now, Kida, stop goofing off.
紀田 ふざけるんじゃない！
Sonohara, you wouldn't misunderstand and start weird rumors, would you?
園原 勘違いして 変な噂流さないでくれよな
Does she look like the frivolous kind of woman?
彼女がそんな軽薄な女に見えますか？
You're right, I'll leave her with you.
そうだよな
頼むぞ まったく
Don't worry, I'll be the one spreading rumors!
むしろ 噂はオレが流すんで 安心してくださ～い
Does this make me a crusader of justice for the moment?
さしずめ正義の味方ってところ？
I was so cool just now, wasn't I?
今のオレ 格好よくねぇ？
Anyone would fall for me after that.
普通 ほれちゃうだろ
Kida? And Sonohara?
紀田君？ 園原さんも
Could you have come at a worse time?
なんてタイミングで現れやがる…
Sorry for the wait.
お待たせ～
Here.
ほい
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
But still, you should be careful.
でもな マジで気ぃつけた方がいいぜ
Most of the rumors about Nasujima are mostly just
that, but it is true he's laid his hands on a student.
那須島の野郎 噂は大半が噂だけど
教え子に手ぇ出したってのはマジだから
Eh?!
A second-year student named Niekawa Haruna transferred out during the second term.
贄川春奈って２年の先輩でさ
去年の２学期ごろ転校したんだが
Apparently the reason was that people
would find out she was dating Nasujima.
それがどうも那須島とつきあってるのがバレそうになったってんだよ
Really?
マジで!?
No one knows whether she wanted to transfer, whether
Nasujima threatened her into it, or if the school forced her.
自分からやめたのか 那須島に脅されたのか
学校が転校させたのかは分かんないけど
Anyway, if something happens to you,
Mikado and I will do something about it.
まっ なんかあったらオレと帝人でなんとかするから
Right, Mikado?
なあ 帝人
あっ… うん
I don't totally grasp the situation, but I'll do whatever I can.
状況がいまいち飲み込めないけど
僕にできることはなんでもするよ
Ugh. This is where you're supposed to say, "I might not
be able to do it, but I'll be able to with the power of love!"
バカだな お前 こういうときは
「僕にできないことだろうが 愛の力でやってみせるよ」
You're not a man if you don't say something to that effect.
くらいのこと言ってのけないと男じゃないぜ
Eh? Isn't that a contradiction?
矛盾じゃん
I'm just going with the flow.
ノリだから
More importantly, about before...
それより この前のこと
Huh?
Those girls who were bullying you were from your middle school, right?
いじめてた子たち同中なんでしょ？
H-How did you know?
な… なんで 知ってるんですか？
Well, listening to your conversation, I figured they had to be.
いや あの会話からしてそうとしか…
中学のころは実力のある子に助けられてて
Like a, "you were saved by a good person, but now that she's disappeared they've come back," kind of thing.
その子がいなくなった途端に昔のヤツらがまた来たと
Hmm? Your friend's disappeared? And no one's found her yet...
なんだっけ？ いなくなった友達
まだ見つからないんだ
It's Harima Mika from our class, isn't it?
うちのクラスの張間美香さんだよね？
Mika's just marked as absent at school, but she
hasn't been home since before opening ceremonies.
美香さん 学校には欠席ってことになってますけど
入学式の前から一度も家に帰ってないんです
That's totally something you should tell the police about.
それ 思いっ切り警察沙汰じゃん
She contacted my cell phone and Harima's home.
私の携帯と張間さんの家には連絡が入ってるんです
She said, "I'm going on a trip to heal my broken heart. Don't worry."
「ちょっと傷心旅行に行ってます気にしないで」って
A trip to heal her broken heart? Did something happen?
傷心旅行？ 何かあったの？
Umm...will you promise to listen without freaking out?
それは… あの…
驚かないで聞いてくれますか？
I'm not surprised by much anymore
after what's happened these past few days.
この数日で 大抵のことには驚かなくなったから
Harima...is a stalker.
張間さんはストーカーなんです
I see.
なるほど
So that's what you were asking that guy about.
つまりこの前君が詰問していた男だな？
Mika went on her broken-heart trip after being
dumped by the guy she was stalking—er, courting.
あいつに付きまとっていた…
いや 求愛していた美香ちゃんが
I guess we can't do anything but leave it to her family.
振られたから傷心旅行に出たと
If she still doesn't come back, all we can do is call the police.
そいつは家族に任せるしかないなぁ
いよいよとなったら警察に言うだろ
Was she a close friend to you, Sonohara?
園原さんとは仲よかったの？
What's with the interrogative?
なんだ？ その疑問形は
It's true that we were always together.
いつも一緒にいたのは確かです
I guess his intuition is good with some things.
こいつは妙なところで勘がいい
I'm awkward with a lot of things and not very good at
dealing with people, but Mika would always pull me through.
私はいろいろと不器用で 人ともうまくつきあえないんですけど
それをいつも引っ張ってくれたのが美香さんで…
I felt bad that she even chose the same high school as me.
わざわざ私と同じ高校を選んでくれて
私はそれが申し訳なくて
Well, that's...
それは…
Even if you think Mika didn't want to let go of her because she
was using her to stand out, you shouldn't actually say that, Mikado.
君という引き立て役を手放したくなかったからじゃ…
なんてことは思っても口に出しちゃいけないよ 帝人君
I know.
分かってます
Eh?
You know what?
何が？
That she was just using me to look cool.
私が美香さんの引き立て役だってこと
And I used her as well.
それで 私も彼女を利用してたんです
I thought that life would be easier, that
I couldn't live without depending on her.
依存して生きていく方が楽だから
そうしないと生きていけないと思ってたから
Okay...
But now I don't think it's that important.
でも今はそれほど必要だとは思えなくなって
I've adjusted...to living without her.
慣れてきたんです 彼女がいない状況に
I became a class rep because she wanted to,
so I figured I should at least do it in her stead.
クラス委員になったのも
クラス委員は張間さんがやりたがっていた役職で
せめて私が代わりにやらなきゃと思って
I felt like if I became a class rep, then I could surpass her.
クラス委員になれば彼女を追い越せるような気がして
That's kind of like cheating though, don't you think?
ずるいですよね こんなの…
In my opinion, what's cheating is telling people all that.
それをわざわざ人に言うのがいちばんずるいと思う
It sounds like you're trying to get someone to forgive you.
なんだか それで誰かに許してもらおうとしてるみたいだ
Trying to surpass Harima is the right thing to do.
張間さんより上を目指そうっていうのは正しい選択だよ
So you should hold your head high and be more confident.
だからもっと胸を張って 堂々としてればいいんじゃないかな
Umm...
You're right.
そうですね ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
That's what I like about this guy.
こいつのこういうところがオレは結構気に入ってる
Kida!
紀田君！
You're so lame!
格好悪ぃ！
"Lame," huh?
格好悪ぃって…
Eh? The strongest in Ikebukuro?
ええ～ 池袋最強？
Yes, the strongest.
そう 最強
You from some magazine?
おじさん 雑誌の人？
Whaddya mean by "strongest?" That's too funny.
最強って何？ 超ウケる
If you're talking about the strongest person in Ikebukuro, it's gotta be that black biker.
そりゃ 最強っつったら
あれ 黒いバイクのヤツ
I've heard of that.
知ってる
He has no head, right?
首がないんでしょう？
Like, no way!
うそ～
What about The Slasher?
あとは 切り裂き魔とか？
Oh yeah, that.
ああ あれね～
But you'd hafta say the strongest group here is The Dollars, right?
でも 今この街最強ったらダラ－ズでしょ？
The Dollars?
ダラーズ？
Yeah, The Dollars!
そう ダラーズ！
I go a different way from here.
じゃあ 私 ここで
Thank you very much for today.
今日はありがとうございました
See you tomorrow.
じゃあ また明日
Bye bye, Anri!
バイバ～イ 杏里ちゃ～ん
I've thought of this before, but maybe
we'd find that Mika girl with Yagiri after all.
思ったんだけど
やっぱり矢霧君と美香って子は一緒にいるんじゃないかな？
You mean like a stalker and her victim?
ストーカーと被害者が？
Maybe she abducted him.
矢霧君がその子に誘拐されてるとか
I get it.
なるほど
People are missing...
人捜しか どうすればいいんだろ？
But how are we going to look for them?
Just leave them be. She said not to worry.
ほうっておけよ 彼女ももういいっつってたじゃん
Only an organized group would be able to pull this off...
やっぱり組織か何かがないと無理かな？
Like The Dollars.
ダラーズとか
Mikado...
帝人… お前まさかダラーズに入りたいなんて思ってる？
You're not thinking of joining The Dollars, are you?
Eh? No. No way!
いやぁ～ まさか
You better not.
マジやめとけよ
People only join gangs when they're young and impressionable.
カラーギャングなんてのは若気の至りで
Besides, most people regret joining them.
大抵あとで後悔するもんだ
Umm...yeah, but we're still young and impressionable...
うん
でも僕らまだ若気の至りだし
I'm spent.
マジ だりぃ～
Why?
何が？ ん？
I was extremely depressed before Mikado came to Ikebukuro.
帝人が池袋に来る前
オレはマジで落ち込んでたんだ
I'm able to make it through the day thanks to lots of people...
今はなんとかこんな感じでやってけてんのは
まあ いろんな人のお陰なんだが
But it's also thanks to Mikado.
帝人のお陰でもあるわけで…
He's new to Ikebukuro and still vulnerable to the sweltering atmosphere.
あいつは今池袋に来たばっかで
この街の熱気にやられっぱなし
Because he's new, he's more likely to get into trouble.
危なっかしくて見てられねぇ
That's all?! It can't sell much worse than that!
I can douse him with cold water, but when I look into his gleaming eyes,
冷や水ぶっかけてやることもできるが
目を輝かせてるあいつを見てると そんな気にもならない
I know not even that will work.
That's why I try to be with him as much as I can.
だから せめていつも一緒にいてやろうとしてるんだが…
I don't want him to get near the darkness this city holds.
できれば あいつにはこの街の闇には近づいてほしくない
Or me.
オレも…
Bang.
I told myself I'd never...go there again.
もう二度とあっちには行かないと心に決めたんだ
Saika has entered the chat room.
Stronger
Strong, Love, Hope
I, want, to hope
I, want, stronger, love
Strong, person, to love
Hope, me, mother, mother
Mother
Saika has left the chat room.
Could someone be spamming us?
It's like an alien.
Maybe it's laughing...
How scary...
Look, the kanji for mother is "haha," so...
No, I'm not afraid it's an alien.
Or anything like that.
TsumiUta?
罪歌？
Or maybe it's "Zaika."
それとも罪歌かな？
"Zaika" as in "property?"
I'll look into it later.
あとで調べておくよ
More importantly, Celty, I have a job for you.
それより セルティ 仕事だよ
It's from Mr. Shiki of the Awakusu Association again.
また粟楠会の四木さんから
It's not that great a job, but will you do it?
筋がいい仕事じゃないけど やってくれるかい？
Another courier job?
また運び屋？
Yes, it's a courier job.
そう 運び屋
Although, you have to start by getting the merchandise back.
といってもブツを取り戻すところからやらなきゃならないんだが
I don't know what the merchandise is, or I
should say it was a "don't ask, don't tell" situation.
ブツが何かは聞いてない
というか 聞かないのがお互いのためだし
Understood.
分かってる
Okay, now about the item. The guy who stole it is running around somewhere.
で そのブツだけど
盗んだヤツが逃げ回ってるらしい
You know where most of the hiding spots are,
so you should be able to corner him easily.
だいたいの潜伏場所は分かってるから
すぐに追い詰められるはず
Roger.
了解
Be careful; that Slasher's been out and about lately.
最近 切り裂き魔が出没してるらしいから気をつけてね
The Slasher?
切り裂き魔？
Yeah, The Slasher. He appeared again.
そう 切り裂き魔
また出たらしいよ
He just leaves after inflicting wounds, but never kills anyone.
殺さずに傷だけ負わせて去っていくんだＹＯ
Then you can't call him the strongest, can you?
そりゃ最強とは言えないな
The strongest person in this city's gotta be...
この街で最強っつったら やっぱり…
Simon from Russia Sushi.
「露西亜寿し」のサイモン
That information guy moved over to Shinjuku, but what about him?
今は新宿に移ったけど
情報屋のあいつ
Orihara Izaya.
折原臨也
No, it's gotta be...
それなら やっぱあいつだろ
Heiwajima Shizuo!
平和島静雄！
The strongest Color Gang?
カラーギャング最強？っつったら
Nowadays it's The Dollars?
今はダラーズＹＯ
But The Dollars don't have a color.
ダラーズは色がないんだ
That yellow gang held the most sway until last year.
去年までは黄色いのが幅を利かせてたけどね
Yellow?
黄色…
Yeah, they're called The Yellow Scarves.
黄巾賊っつってＹＯ…
I heard they had an insane brawl with
The Blue Squares and lots of people got taken out.
去年 ブルースクウェアっつう別のカラーギャングとガチで
やり合って共倒れしたって聞いたけどね～
Yeah, I heard they're back in the game.
いや それが最近また復活したらしい
Come on, keep the orders coming!
さあ～ ドンドン注文してネ！
We have Engawa scallops. They're cheap, they're cheap!
エンガ～ワ ホタ～テ 安いヨ…
Say, don't you see them a lot these days?
そういえば 最近よく見かけません？
See what?
何が？
Guys in yellow, right? So you did notice.
黄色いのでしょ？
やっぱ気がついてた？
Yellow? You mean—
黄色って まさか…
The Mellow Scars!
ひょうきん族
You mean The Yellow Scarves.
黄巾賊だろ
Yeah, that's it.
そう それ
That's Hermes' line.
今のエルメスね
They should've been eradicated after that battle with The Blue Squares.
いや 黄巾賊はブルースクウェアとの抗争で壊滅したはずだ
Yeah, I guess.
そうね
Their boss supposedly left.
あそこのボスは手を引いてるはずだから…
Just call me over any time. Ah, welcome!
ヘイ ラッシャイ！
Can you please tell me about The Dollars?
ダラーズについて教えてもらえませんか？
Huh?
My friend's thinking of joining them, but I want to stop him.
オレのダチが首突っ込もうとしてて 止めたいんです
Why're you asking us?
なんでオレたちに聞く？
Well, I can't ask anyone else.
いや… ほかに聞ける人がいないから
You wouldn't want to ask Orihara Izaya anyway.
まさか折原臨也に聞くわけにいかないもんねぇ
It's not like we know much about The Dollars.
いや ダラーズについちゃオレたちだって詳しいわけじゃない
But I'll tell you everything we do know.
知ってることは全部話してやるがな
Sometimes...this city can almost swallow you whole.
時々 この街に飲み込まれそうになる
However, I won't let you go that far, Mikado.
だが 帝人
お前をあっちには行かせない
Mikado?
帝人？
Sorry!
悪ぃ
You can't just do that.
そりゃないんじゃないの？
You can tell just by lookin' that we be Yellow Scarves, can'tchya?
オレたち黄巾賊だって見たら分かるよね？
Yagiri!
矢霧君！
Huh?
あれ？ 張間美香じゃない…
That's not...Harima Mika.
I don't know who you are, but don't interfere with our flight of love.
誰だか知らないが
僕たちの愛の逃避行を邪魔しないでくれ
"Flight of love...?"
愛の逃避行って…
Let's go.
行こう
Then who is that?
でも 誰なんだ？ あれ
Kida!
紀田君
Are you guys really in The Yellow Scarves?
あんたら本当に黄巾賊？
Yeah, of course!
決まってんだろ
I'm asking you because I can't tell.
分かんないから聞いてんだよ
You...
こいつ…
Kida!
き… 紀田君！
Oh no, Mikado, why you, too?
おいおい 帝人 なんでお前まで？
Mo-Monster!
ば… 化け物～！
Huh?
Let's go!
行くぞ！
Man, you had me worried!
お前なぁ 心配掛けやがって
そっちこそ
Same here!
In the end, I might be the one who's dependent upon him.
結局 依存してるのはオレの方なのかもしれない
I guess.
After Mikado came here, I feel like my bravado's turned into real courage.
帝人が来てから
こっち空元気が本物になるような気がしてるんだ
I might just be able to face her without running away now.
今なら…
今度こそ逃げずに 彼女に会うことができるかもしれない
Yes?
はい
The more she expects me to, the more like I'll be able to do it.
そんな気さえしてくるほどに…
I didn't think you'd ever come here again.
もう来てくれないかと思った
Izaya.
臨也さん
Hey.
やあ
How's your boyfriend been?
最近 彼 どう？
He visits me sometimes.
ええ… 時々 来てくれますよ
Like he did just before now.
その前まで…
I'm home.
ただいま～
Haruna, did you make sure to eat?
春奈～ ちゃんと飯食ったか？
Haruna?
春奈～！
Oh, I banned the spammer.
Now it can be peaceful again.
It'd be nice if that were so...
By the way, I heard that members of The Yellow Scarves got slashed.
What are The Yellow Scarves?
Maybe The Slasher is working for The Dollars.
What? No Way!
A war might break out.
The events which occur in this city may
seem completely unrelated upon first glance...
この街で起こっていることは
一見バラバラなようで
But they definitely connect at some point...
きっとどこかでつながっていて
Yo!
And probably hold some twisted knowledge that we can't even fathom.
オレたちには計り知れないいびつな真相を抱え込んでいるんだろう
Good morning, Kida.
Yet...
だけど…
Good morning!
お～はよ！
Good morning, Sonohara.
お… おはよう 園原さん
Good morning.
I just noticed it, but this relationship feels pretty comfortable.
今更気づいたことだが
オレはこの関係が結構居心地がいいらしい
Points will connect with each other eventually...
いつか点と点がつながって
And even if something we can't say right now gets exposed...
今は見えない何かが暴かれるとしても
I believe that our relationship will stay the same.
オレたちの関係は変わらずにいられると 今はそう信じている
制作：LASTZZZ 安静の云 akira アキラ
The Dollars?
ダラーズ？
I can't say much about them.
オレに聞かれても大したことは言えねぇ
Anyway, I'll tell you everything about the already-famous Kaztano Incident.
とりあえず もはや伝説と化したカズターノ事件のてんまつを聞かせよう
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs/
Next time: Run Around.
Also, don't call me Dotachin.
ただし オレのことをドタチンとは呼ぶなよ